Step two: start rumor
(Sheldon:)this comic book store
gives you genital warts.
Step three: buy a big bag
to put the money in.
(Leonard:)It's not that bad.
(Raj:)Hey.
Hi.
(Penny:)Thank you so much for letting me
practice my sales pitch on you.
(Penny:)I really appreciate it.
(Emily:)Sure.
Um, I brought coffee.
(Penny:)I wasn't sure what you like,
so I got
(Penny:)a regular, a cappuccino
and a Chai tea.
(Penny:)Since you like Raj, I thought
you might be into that.
(Emily:)Thanks. If we could get started.
I'm a little busy.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, sure. Let me
just get out my materials.
(Penny:)Leonard gave me this briefcase.
(Penny:)He used to carry it
around in high school.
(Penny:)You can still see the dent
where they whacked him with it.
(clears throat)
(Penny:)Okay, I would like
to talk to you
(Penny:)about our new
birth control pill, Femevra.
(Penny:)Great.
(Penny:)So, Femevra's
triphasic design
(Penny:)provides balanced
hormonal exposure.